# **DUKENBAY URZIYA**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Software developer with experience in high-performing and well-organized architecture applications. Experienced in product design and client relations. Being passionate about creative development and a leader that will be able to innovate. To learn and share all experiences in a way that they can be excited about it like I am.

#### EXPERIENCE

## Software Developer

Kaspi Bank | Jul 2021 - present

- develop and lead algorithmic solutions to implement the task
- building reusable components in Vuejs and implementing MVC by using jQuery and Javascript in the front-end part
- writing unit tests(IntelliJ), writing services and debugging in Siebel (back-end)
- correct and improve the development of an already written process
- develop instructions, write technical documentation
- mentoring juniors, took a part in company culture by sharing knowledge

## Lead Engineer

GATE Insaat Taahhut Sanayi ve Ticaret | Nov 2017 - Jul 2021

- Product code using .NET languages (C#), upgrade, configure and debug the system, provide technical support
- Designed and build architecture of the database in MS SQL Server, monitor documentation, and provide daily, weekly reports
- Analyzing system and preparing monthly/weekly reports for management

## Database and BI Developer

LLP Teksan | Feb 2017 - Oct 2017

- Created and supported database in MS SQL Server
- Maintained Tiger (SAP)
- Prepare KPI and BI reports (Datazen Dashboards). Analyzing sales and prioritizing sales according to sales reports at every city shop

## Oracle Siebel CRM system developer

Borlas Kazakhstan | Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

- Maintenance of Siebel CRM Application
- Supported and developed the system to customer requirements.

#### VOLUNTEER

## Lead Front-end developer

Yolla Startup, Malaysia | Oct 2021 - May 2022

- Building responsive design and reusable components, written technical documentation
- Collaborate remotely with the team
- Build dashboards on React and Typescript during one week

## EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Suleyman Demirel University

Computer Science, B.Sc. | Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

- B.E., engineering and technology
- GPA: 3.53 (4.0). Diploma with honors
- Participated in enterprise project in KazMunayGas, as system administrator, Jun - Aug 2015



## **CONTACT**



Remote



urziya.dukenbay@gmail.com



Portfolio



@urziya-dukenbay



udukenbay

# **SKILLS**

#### FRONT-END:

- HTML and HTML5
- CSS, CSS3, Sass, Styled components
- Responsive Design
- Webpack
- Javascript (ES6)
- jQuery
- Frameworks: React, Vuejs
- Typescript
- MVC
- Unit Test (Unit Framework)

#### BACK-END:

- Java
- C#
- goLang
- Next.js
- Siebel (CRM)
- Unit Test (IntelliJ)

#### DATABASE:

- MS SQL Server
- Pl SQL
- NoSQL

## MISCELLANEOUS:

- NPM | Yarn
- Source control (Git, GitBucket, GitHub)
- CI/CD Automation
- ΔσίΙε
- JIRA, Trello
- Figma
- Unity, 3ds Max
- Cisco, Packet Tracer

# Language

- •••• Kazakh
- •••• Russian
- •••• English
- ••• Turkish
- • German